interface Multiplication {
    id: number;
    question: string;
    answer: number;
  }
  
  const multiplications: Multiplication[] = [
    { id: 1, question: '2 * 4', answer: 8 },
    { id: 2, question: '5 * 3', answer: 15 },
    { id: 3, question: '7 * 2', answer: 14 },
    { id: 4, question: '9 * 6', answer: 54 },
    { id: 5, question: '3 * 8', answer: 24 },
    { id: 6, question: '4 * 5', answer: 20 },
    { id: 7, question: '6 * 7', answer: 42 },
    { id: 8, question: '10 * 2', answer: 20 },
    { id: 9, question: '8 * 9', answer: 72 },
    { id: 10, question: '11 * 4', answer: 44 },
    { id: 11, question: '3 * 7', answer: 21 },
    { id: 12, question: '6 * 9', answer: 54 },
    { id: 13, question: '8 * 2', answer: 16 },
    { id: 14, question: '4 * 5', answer: 20 },
    { id: 15, question: '10 * 10', answer: 100 },
    { id: 16, question: '11 * 3', answer: 33 },
    { id: 17, question: '12 * 8', answer: 96 },
    { id: 18, question: '9 * 4', answer: 36 },
    { id: 19, question: '7 * 6', answer: 42 },
    { id: 20, question: '15 * 2', answer: 30 },
    { id: 21, question: '2 * 3', answer: 6 },
    { id: 22, question: '4 * 6', answer: 24 },
    { id: 23, question: '7 * 8', answer: 56 },
    { id: 24, question: '9 * 5', answer: 45 },
    { id: 25, question: '12 * 3', answer: 36 },
    { id: 26, question: '10 * 7', answer: 70 },
    { id: 27, question: '11 * 9', answer: 99 },
    { id: 28, question: '6 * 2', answer: 12 },
    { id: 29, question: '8 * 4', answer: 32 },
    { id: 30, question: '15 * 10', answer: 150 },
  ];
  
  export default multiplications;
  